(Penny:)I smell Chinese food.
(Sheldon:)It's actually Thai.
(Sheldon:)You're slipping.
(Penny:)Are Leonard and Priya here?
(Sheldon:)They went to Catalina
for the weekend.
(Penny:)Oh. Where's Raj?
(Sheldon:)At home, forbidding it.
(Penny:)How about Howard?
(Sheldon:)I'm given to understand
(Sheldon:)his mother grounded him
for running away.
(Penny:)Oh, okay.
(Penny:)Well, I guess it's just
the two of us, huh?
(Sheldon:)Actually, it's
the three of us.
(Penny:)AMY
What up, bestie?
(Amy(on webcam):)Good news.
(Amy(on webcam):)Thanks to you, I was able
to make a rhesus monkey cry
(Amy(on webcam):)like a disgraced televangelist.
(Bernadette:)Great.
(Amy:)So, you feeling better?
(Howard:)Not really.
(Amy:)Sheldon, you have
a guest who's upset.
(Sheldon:)Right. I'll make tea.
(Penny:)- Sweetie, it's okay. I don't want tea.
- I'm sorry. It's not optional.